HANNAH LEONG

TECHNOLOGY DEGREE APPRENTICE

hannah.leo64@gmail.com

07948381115

www.linkedin.com/in/hannah-leo

PROFILE

I am currently a final year technology degree apprentice with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC), studying computer science at the University of Birmingham. I specialise in software engineering but also have an interest in cyber security, image processing and robotics.

EDUCATION

BSc Computer Science with Digital Technology Partnership, University of Birmingham (2018–2022)

Degree apprenticeship with year in industry sponsored by PwC

Nonsuch High School for Girls (2011–2018)

A-levels: A*, A, A, B in Mathematics, Further Mathematics, Computer Science and Physics, with an A* in EPQ GCSEs: 1 A**, 7 A*, 3 A, 1 B

EXPERIENCE

2018-Present

Technology Degree Apprentice • PwC

2018: Summer placement spent designing and building a chatbot, implementing Google Cloud Platform capabilities in an Agile method. 2020-2021: Year placement working on projects ranging from a global mobility tool to a personalised online learning platform. Gained experience with Microsoft Azure services, bug testing and fixing, and multiple programming languages (e.g. C#, JavaScript, SQL, YAML, Python)

2017-2018

Tutor • First Class Learning

Leading group tuition sessions for children up to GCSE age

2014-2018

Restaurant Worker • Gold Medal House

Delivering takeaway meals

KEY SKILLS -

Problem solving

Organisation

Teamwork

Leadership

Critical thinking

"Keen to learn" - Inquisitive

"Determined", "Analytical", "Hard working", "Enthusiastic"

Programming languages:

- Java
- Python
- C#
- YAML
- SQL
- JavaScript

VOLUNTEERING

2017-2018

Student Mentor • Nonsuch High School

Supporting younger pupils with their studies and sitting in as a teaching aid in computer science classes

2016-2017

Donation Organiser • St Raphael's Hospice Charity ShopSorting through and organising charity shop donations

2014-2017

Craft Leader • Children's Holiday Club

Helping organise and plan crafts for a children's annual holiday club

2015-2016

Animal Care • Bobtails Rabbit and Guinea Pig Rescue

Animal care at a local rescue centre